Today we are going big or we are going
home. Or we could accidentally look at
Ender Bro.
There's even a sign that says don't look
at Ender Bro. It It upsets him. He
doesn't even move anymore. He just He
just starts getting angry in his boat.
What's up, bro? Oh, that's messing with
my eyes. Terrifying. Got my pesky bird
here and we are going big on the sewer
games. We're going to go ahead and we're
going to make a big play slashmove.
We've got quite a few little bits in
here, but I want this sewer to be full.
So, let's go on a little excursion to
the surface. We'll yink one of these.
We'll yink one of these. Super annoying
to rebuild.
We will yink one of these. H, why not?
We'll take this one as well. And now we
remake them in the sewer. Calm down,
bro. We've yonked a container, a tree,
which I don't recommend because that was
not fun to rebuild, a container, and a
sign for the station. So, that's a
pretty good start. But it's not all. I
have another play that I'd like to make
for not just putting stuff in the sewer.
Did I look at Enderra? I did.
I'm sorry. How did I even look at you?
Or was it you? I have an idea for a
trap/care,
but I'm not sure how it's going to go.
Let's try. First of all, I've got to go
and pick something up from my base, and
it is right here. I need this gold block
and I need two shulker boxes full of
ender pearls. I also need all the name
tags I can get my hands on, which in
this case is not actually many. And
don't ask me how I got this jelly cat
head because you won't like the answer.
My plan here is simple. I remove one
diamond block. That is all. And I
replace it with a gold block, right?
Something that will annoy someone. The
trap is simple. We create a bunch of
mobs just above the gold block in the
form of endermites. Now, how I spawn
these endermites in, I haven't quite
figured out. And then we right click
them and silence them. Question is, how
do I get multiple of these to behave?
Oh, this isn't going to go well. No, no,
no, no. Help. Help. Help. Help. Help.
Help. Help.
H.
That's not what I wanted.
The problem with spawning these in is
that it teleports you. It teleports you
into the very trap I'm trying to create.
There we go. This is working out. Just
need to silence the ones that aren't
silenced. No. Not again. Not again. Not
again. Not again. Not again. Not again.
Oh, for goodness sake. Really?
Uh-oh. I'm running out of emergency
elytra. You know what? I need a bed in
there. This is going to be a lot more
painful than I initially thought. Three
more. Just three more. Last one. Last
one. Last one. No. Yes. That's it.
That's it. Just get in there. Boom.
That's it. We're done. No more ender
pearls for me. No more dying to this
stupid stuff.
We did it. We did it. Just don't let
them out. That's the key. Don't let them
out. And we seal them up. And they don't
despawn when you relog. They are all set
and ready to go. They aren't making a
noise.
And we are
we are done.
Just clearly jumped off a building
there. So the plan is, if you haven't
already figured it out, Cleo comes in
here and sees a spot out of place and
maybe we place the diamond block there.
So she knows which one needs to be
replaced. This will then trigger, of
course, once she breaks that 20 or so
endermites to fall down and well
hopefully shock her a little bit. So
that's fun. It does bother me though,
doesn't it? It really does bother me.
And I think that's probably Oh my Oh my,
that is the most amazing armor stand I
think I've ever seen been done on
Hermitcraft. This is literally my
favorite thing on the server right now.
Look at that. It's perfect, man. It
makes me want to bring back a superhero
of some kind. Look at that. I just
literally jumped off a building like
that. That's what I look like. Maybe not
quite as cool. But anyway, let's head
over to the base. Actually, I've just
received a message from Tango, who says
he's got something to give me, which is
probably not a good sign at all. And he
said he'd meet me at a quiway town.
Hey, Gran.
Hey, dude. What's going on? I like your
helmet.
I Oh, you Oh. Oh, sorry. Hold on. Pardon
me. Let me
Oh, it was it was a real helmet. I
thought you changed your skin.
No, it is actually a helmet. Yeah.
Uh, so I got a I got a little offer for
you here today. Might be interested in
if if no one's around here. I You're uh
you swap bases with Zet, right?
Yeah. And I'm pretty keen to swap back
soon cuz I've
Yeah. I It is a luxurious, you know,
cave he's got there. But I'd imagine you
want to get back to the mansion.
Yeah. Yeah, I do. And And he's been
tidying up, so he's done a lot of chores
and I'm quite Yeah, I'm ready to go
back.
Okay. Okay, then. I think I might have
what you need. I have a book here. Okay.
Now, I don't know if you know, but Zed,
like right at the beginning of the
season, he opened up a shop where he
sold kind of IUS to people, and I bought
one
the the 2D Zaf that's like over there
somewhere.
Yeah. Yeah. It's like five bucks tall or
something. Yeah. Yeah.
It sold out instantly. So, yeah.
Yeah. And he never restocked or
anything. But anyways, I've been sitting
on this book for I think all of season 7
now, waiting for just that time. And
it's not going to happen. But I think
you might have a use for it. So, take a
read and let me see if you can uh piece
it together.
Feel free to pop into Zed's base at any
time. You can put your feet up, rummage
in the chest, sleep in the bed, use the
contraptions, make it like your second
home. You are also permitted to take any
item you like. Oh.
Oh, Tango.
Tango. Tang. This is exactly
what I need.
Yeah.
Okay. Just walk in there and uh put your
feet up, make a jerk of yourself, and
then ask for the deed back. What's the
price? Good.
Well, uh I mean, I'll be honest. I can
remember you just just for the sheer
entertainment of watching this happen,
man. You know,
a favor. A favor in the future, we'll
say. Is that Is that a deal?
Okay, I'll I'll write you up an IOU. Is
there a Can you see an anvil anywhere? I
might I'll end up regretting this. I
know. I always do. One green I owe you.
There you go. These things are gold
dust. You traded. You traded up.
I love it. Boom.
I love it. This is Yeah,
this is it. I could get the I have the
get out of jail free card.
It It's a free ticket to paradise. Yep.
Oh, yeah. Thanks, dude. Oh, this is
perfect. I was going to do some sort of
elaborate heist, but this is perfect. I
Easy, easy.
Wonderful. All right. Thank you very
much, dude. Bye.
This is perfect. With this book, I don't
need to do any sort of elaborate heist
scheme. I can just give him this and we
have to swap back. Well, to be honest, I
don't Thinking about this for a second.
Just just just for a second, there's
nothing in here that says I actually
have to give him his base back. I could
just simply own both of them. I think we
ought to give it back, though. I'm just
saying it's a possibility. We We'll
probably give it back, right? Right. I
mean, we don't have to. I haven't
actually seen ZedF Online too recently,
and I actually came up with an idea for
a contraption. I feel like if I'm going
to swap back, I at least need to add
something to the cave of contraptions.
Apart from just sort of tidying it up,
I'm pretty happy with how this has gone.
The mushrooms add a lot. I think I've
added enough lighting to keep it safe.
And I don't know, it's just I think it's
a lot cleaner in here. However, it feels
kind of wrong of me not to add something
contraption-wise,
and I think I've got one. So, Zedaf
doesn't have a pretty good food source
from what I can tell. He's got bamboo.
He's got cactus. Nothing you can eat.
Maybe honey, but that's not food. Okay.
So, I I think he doesn't have a
sustainable food source. So, I was
thinking we should do something about
that. And while we're at it, I think we
should maybe make it up here, which
could use a bit of love and attention as
well. So, let me take you through what I
think we should do. And it has a lot to
do with these. So, the idea that I
currently have is a giant chicken head.
Let's let's pretend this is a giant
chicken head. And this is going to spit
out eggs. And it's going to spawn
chickens
inside. It's going to spit eggs into
here into this water stream. And I'm
going to design B I don't know how to
explain this, but I'm going to design
the chicken's life. So, there's going to
be a series of rooms and the chickens
get forced and pushed through it. They
live out their life long enough to make
it to the end. You know what? This is so
difficult to explain. It's a really
simple concept. It's a chicken farm, but
it's a fun chicken farm. So, I think
that's what we should do right now. And
I don't know how I'm going to fit it all
in here, but I'm that's what I'm
thinking we do. So, let's hop into a
time lapse and get this thing made.
[Music]
Check it out. We've got a proper
greenhouse with real trees and Scar just
turned up out of nowhere and decided to
help. So, I am not complaining at all.
Uh we we actually just sat in a call. We
were just chatting about stuff. He was
like, "Yeah, I'll help you." And uh he
was also very kind in helping me design
these laptops here. But check out what
is going on here. So, it's not very
efficient at all. It throws an egg every
now and again, just in a sort of a
typical Zaf kind of way. And this is
happening. So, let me just take you
through what I've built here. So, this
is mama mama chicken. And she spits out
eggs. Bof down here, and then the
chickens make their way into life. So,
what we've got here is uh the hospital
where they are born and we've kind of
kitting it kitted it out with some beds
and stuff. Then they move on to school,
which I think is it's quite cute. And
they learn their ABCs. And then of
course they make their way and they fall
down here. And then they go and for some
reason they all get stuck here. And then
they move on to the office where they
must work for the majority of their
life. And then they end up here in uh
the the graveyard of the whole thing.
And then they should in theory walk onto
this. Oh, I've I've trapped myself. I've
put myself in my Oh, no. Yep. Fell for
my own thing. The thing is, we've got a
lot of chickens all trying to get to
mama chicken cuz there's like a bunch of
chickens in here that are spawning the
eggs and they are all trying to get to
it. It's only when they are adults,
which isn't necessarily a bad thing, but
it's only when they're adults that
they're going to walk off and hopefully
end up in the campfire. So, I do have a
workound and I might give it a go. But
look, there's been a lot of chickens
that's gone through this system. And let
me tell you how many uh cooked chickens
we got. None. I know that Zedaf's farms
are incredibly inefficient,
but I seem to have created a farm so
inefficient that it doesn't work at all.
I'm yet to get a single cooked chicken
and we've just got a pile up in the
office. Ah,
not not good. So, my elegant solution to
this instead of fixing my incredibly
inefficient farm, I think Zedaf will
appreciate this. Craft up a furnace,
cook some raw chicken, and simply
pretend that it works. I'm hiding my
failure here. Maybe Zaf can make this
thing work. Maybe it's not as flawed as
I thought. You know, the problem with
this thing is I thought of this idea
where the chickens go through life, but
I didn't test it. You see, I just I went
ahead and I went on a very brave
assumption that this whole thing would
work out, and it didn't. It didn't work
out. It doesn't work. But who knows?
Maybe he'll come up with something.
These guys will eventually grow up and
then in theory should make their way
over there. But I'm not even sure if
they're going to walk into the campfire.
It doesn't look like they will.
So, I'm just going to start pushing them
in. Oh, there we go.
Now we're cooking for real. It works.
Once they're all adults, it actually
works. The issue is, are you for real?
Campfires don't cook chicken. That is an
oversight. Back to the drawing board,
and it is working. I've actually managed
to reconfigure this last bit so that it
genuinely harvests roast chicken. It's
the most inefficient farm of all time.
As you can see, most of the chickens
just despawned and turned into eggs. So,
not great. But Zedaf is actually online
right now. I've got my book and I'm able
to swap back. So, I think it's time to
say goodbye. I've actually got all my
Shulker boxes with me and it is time to
say goodbye to this lovely place. This
is like a really chill place now. And
I'm glad I managed to get this done
before we do the swap back. So, let's go
and grab everything and then head over.
I think it's gonna be good. I think it's
going to be good to get back in the back
to the old mansion. Now, this was a a
well needed, much deserved sort of break
from the huge project that the mansion
was. Got some fresh energy for it. And
so, we'll take one last look. Actually,
we're probably going to have to come
back here and show Zaf what we've done.
So, we'll be back very shortly in here.
Let's head over to the base and reveal
our top card. this the IOU that's going
to get me back my mansion. I hope he's I
hope he's done cleaning up. Oh, there he
is. Let's hop into a call with him. Hey,
Zaf.
Oh, hey. You all right? I'm You've come
to laugh at me sorting your stuff out.
I've actually um I've somewhat come to
relieve you of this duty. I I feel like
you've probably done enough sorting. And
um I've got something to show you.
Let me see
this. Take a little read of that.
Home from home. Feel free to pop into
Zpace at any time. You can put your feet
up. You're also permitted to take any
This is my zoucher.
It is a zoucher. And I would like the
deed to the mansion.
What?
And then you'll have my base and the
mansion.
Technically, yeah.
I think I've just made you homeless.
No.
Um,
okay. I mean, a zouch is a zoucher,
right? nostalgia.
Oh, why am I Why am I such a stickler
for the rules, man?
Hey,
um, can I just stay in the warm for a
while or have I got to leave now?
Um, well, I I mean, I'm not I'm not
really going to keep your base from you.
I'm I was going to gift it back. We'll
do we'll do a we'll do a a nice swap
back, shall we? But I thought I I just
wanted to see your face, really.
Oh, man. My
I genuinely just thought, what am I
going to do? I got to build a dirt house
all over again or something. Oh,
no. Don't worry. Your your base is your
base is now yours. And I think that is
that's it. We have officially swapped
back.
Excellent. Oh, well, in that case, here,
look, here's some junking
out. In
in fact, in fact, I might just uh make
myself at home real quick.
Don't you dare. Don't you dare. I might
just uh just put Yeah, just Oh, that's
better, isn't it? I've just I carry all
this stuff around with me for ages and
now there's more space in the base to
put all this stuff back, which is
brilliant. That's You know, you've just
gone and
I'm burning these vouchers. These were a
mistake.
This is all the stuff that I've
accumulated working on your base. So, I
will sort this out. Although, I did say
that about all of my chest monsters
throughout this season.
Yeah, man. It was It was absolute
nightmares going through that stuff.
It's not even done. It's about 50%
complete. So, you've you've inherited
all that mess back.
So, can you show me what you've done
apart from tidying up? Have you done
anything else?
Yeah, sure. I've added some
contraptions, believe it or not. You
know all about them having been in my
base. Um, so if you head on up here,
I'll I'll show you how they work. As
with all of my contraptions, they
definitely need a manual because they're
deadly otherwise.
Okay.
Um, so
Wait, can I just try and figure it out?
Yeah, go for it.
Do I have to fly in and then press the
button?
That's it.
Oh, is that it?
Can I press it?
Give it a go, man. Yeah, I'll ride the
other side up.
Okay. See, you're on the top floor.
You might want to tuck your tuck your
head in a little bit. Oh, okay. This
doesn't not sure.
It's much faster to fly up.
Well, sure. It's It's also much less
boring.
It is much less boring. Oh, and it goes
back down on its own. Wait, wait. Is
there one on the other side? Oh, there
it is.
Oh, no. I I trigger I triggered it. I
triggered it.
That is really smart. I would have never
been able Oh, there it is. I found it.
This is amazing.
Nice. Well, we'll come back down and
I'll show you the second contraption I
built. Hopefully it is night time as
well, which is perfect.
Give me a second. Making my way. Hello.
Hello.
All right. I like it.
I like it a lot.
Thanks. Good. The sec the second one
here is the uh the counterult. It's
called
the counterult.
Yeah. If you if you want to sleep in the
bed and then um if you just leave the
bed like you get, you know, go in the
bed and then hop straight back out
again.
Okay.
As if you've slept in the morning.
That's it. Now, if you just press double
double jump and get into fly mode.
Oh, it did. Okay. If you be facing
forward, you normally get catapulted
out.
All right, I'm going to try again. I'm
going to try again.
Okay, then I just look straight
forwards.
Yeah, that's it.
Beautiful.
Oh, I'm a cow, dude. I'm stuck in here
forever.
You might die.
Oh, I will die. Zed. dead.
It's your contraption, man. I mean,
don't don't be telling me about it. At
least you slept.
You've made a machine that kills me.
Hold on. You show me. You show me.
I'll I'll show you how it's done. Okay.
Right. So, you get in bed.
Yeah.
You leave the bed.
Get into fly mode.
Yeah.
What?
And then you die. Right. That's how it
works.
So, you've just made a you've just made
a killing machine. Really? You just
pretty much. Um, yeah, this one still
needs a bit of work.
You tested this. Has this ever worked?
It worked great the first few times I
tried it. Hold on. It will work
eventually.
This doesn't seem like it's worth it.
This will work.
What? Cows, come on. Work with me here.
Hey. Hey. I I died in a quite a a
thrusty kind of manner there.
Your body your body started going.
It's half worked.
Yeah. I I'm not sure it's going to work,
Zed. I I think you made a kill box.
I I have I have I I tell you what,
before I leave at some point, I'll have
a little tinker with it and seeing if I
can get it to work. But you you might be
stuck with a killbox. Whatever you do,
don't sleep in this bed. Okay,
perfect. I love it. But other than that,
man, have have fun back in your mansion.
Can I uh show you what I've done to your
base? You might have already seen my
video, but I have already I have done
some other things that you won't have
seen.
I would love to see what you've done in
my base. Oh, I'm so happy calling it my
base again.
Oh man,
reveal time
is beautiful.
You broke You broke the door.
I hope that you No, I didn't. I never
use the door cuz I don't have a bow and
arrow. And actually, I'll tell you what,
Zed, that's different to how I saw it
the other day. I don't know whether
someone's been messing with it, but it
broke on its own. I haven't touched it.
What?
I haven't touched it.
It seems when you turn up, all of the
contraptions I build break the beauties
wise. Look at this all. It's like a
enchanted cave fairy tale.
Yeah, I was I was going to I was
thinking like I I do hope that you
wanted this to be a cave and not some
sort of other structure cuz I just it
was already a cave and I was like and
it's called the cave of contraptions, so
I just kind of rolled with it.
Yeah, definitely. I wasn't expecting to
be as as fungal as uh as you've now made
it. But I kind of like it.
I needed to add a bit a splash of color
in here because it was just all gray.
All gray pretty much apart from the the
honey area. So I thought splash of red,
bit of green as well, and then a more
alive cave.
I love the pillars that are coming down
too. It's it feels like a real cave now
instead of just a
It was a bit a bit unsupported before,
so I added those in. I have got one more
thing to show you. Oh no. Why does that
fill me with dread?
It shouldn't. I just noticed that you
didn't have correct me if I'm wrong. You
didn't have like a proper food farm. You
got honey, but there's no food.
Yeah, no food at all. No.
Right. Well, I've I've tried to embody
your mentality and I've created this
place
up here.
Green.
There's actual greenery here. And you'll
notice that there's a chicken head. What
it does is it shoots eggs into this hole
here. There's actually one down there
now. And they make their way through
life
and they pop out here. So they're
they're born in the hospital. You see
over here?
I see. Yeah.
And then they make their way to school
and they they learn their ABCs and
KFC's, right?
Fantastic.
Yeah. And then they go to office life
and that's where we do. Yeah. There's
office life. So they're working in an
office and then and then it's um it's
time. It's you know inevitable. Uh, and
then down here they they become tasty
roast chickens.
Look at Oh, so we've had 56 chickens
live full lives. This is this is the
most like nice farm ever. Most people
just kill a chicken immediately whereas
you give it a full happy life.
Full happy life. The only problem is
it's the most inefficient farm that
you've ever seen in your life. You
probably will want to change this
because it I'll be honest with you
doesn't really work.
I hate that smells like all of my
contraptions. So it's perfect.
Oh man, none of my farms have made 56
roast chicken before, so this one's
doing way better than anything.
I love it. It's It's perfect, man. Thank
you so much.
Yay. Okay, wonderful. Well, I'm going to
return to my mansion.
Yeah. And I will stay here in my cave of
contraptions. Gri, my friend, thank you
so much.
It's been awesome, actually. It's been a
really good It's been a really good
experience.
It's been a blast.
It's good to be
home. Thank you very much for watching
and I shall see you in the next episode
where we are back in the mansion. Also,
don't forget to subscribe. If you're if
you're here and you're not subscribed,
why aren't you subscribed? Like
seriously, like very few people make it
to the end of the video. If you're at
the end of this video and you haven't
subscribed, I'm going to start asking
some questions.